I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
Let the shadowings crawl, whisper
I find my grip, feet on ground, pulsing riot, marching out of the dream, slow, quiet, not giving up
Can you see me?
Uh oh.
Where am I?
We're going to take this down.
I don't see anything.
Visual.
I'll pick up the green screen.
Where am I?
Totally missing.
Okay.
I don't know what's going on.
Hold on.
Okay, can you hear me now?
I'm so sorry.
I was gonna say, this is what's gonna happen.
I see, I'll be there as Father Psyche, right?
And she's gonna be a little bit out of breath,
whoo, a little sweaty.
But look, she's gonna knock his ass out.
Like there's Tommy James, completely knocked out.
I'm giving her a little pep talk massage.
She doesn't really need it,
cause she already won, right?
That's what's gonna happen with Tommy James.
Sometimes it gets Alexander if I have to well, I'll throw some rosary beads on the mat and
Just sure has to be a hundred percent not gonna not gonna she she's gonna win a fair and square, but I'm gonna you know
Make sure I'm gonna make sure
What's going on? She was like, you know, Tommy James was on we made you join of course. Yo, you made a join
You're gonna be nice nice
Well, you're never nice, but you're gonna be orgy. Come on up
Yeah, but I think that's gonna be awesome. I can't wait for that fight. I'm gonna everyone put money on you know, you know who
Look, he's gonna be knocked out. I don't even need to if all I need to do is
Give some support.
Hi.
I know that's bothering me deep inside, man.
Something that's bothering me, man.
Tell me.
What's wrong?
My friend Tommy and my friend Alex, I don't want them to fight, man.
I don't want to see my friends fighting.
Like you said, you think it's fun to see your best friends fighting each other?
It hurts.
But I think Alex will kick Tommy.
I love you, Tommy, but Alex, go to kick your ass.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, you see the gals who really kicked Tommy's ass. I don't think so
Don't and you know what Tommy's a gentleman. He would not fight a woman. Tommy would not fight a woman
Are you sure that's one thing I know about my boy T dog
Okay, you know that well, she she wanted she wants to fight and so if it's like, you know, it's consensual
She wants to fight, you know what?
If I was here's what I would say if I was Tommy like listen, I know you're mad at me. You want to fight me
I'm not gonna fight a woman. Go take it out on somebody else
Don't take it out on me because if Tommy ever fought Alex and even if he won or lost
At the end of the day, he's like you fought a woman like all you women fighter
Like, you know, it's a lose lose for Tommy and Tommy's not a retard
He might have been well, but he's so comfortable with it. They're attacking her vocally when she's like, you know far away
Why can't he?
Ever heard Tommy attack out. I never Tommy attack. You miss Tommy. Did you miss careless Cates today?
Yes, I may have yes, I may have I did work
What Tommy attack?
There was a short there's a short a part of the show where I I mean, I'll show you
I'll show you if I can find it but it's still up. Let me see. It's just a short
Maybe it was attacking back
Maybe it was attacking back for being a oh my god. What is that behind you? Who is that kissy? No, move your head away
Move your head back out. What is that?
On the lips that's kind of horny to make me horny
You're making a horny. I don't think it's them, but okay, I mean it's like aliens
It looks like me with a mohawk kiss and be the right on her lips. So actually that
Kind of turning me on. Okay. Well, Joe, it's me and you me and I'm wearing a beetle wig. Oh my god
Okay, oh my gosh, I have a oh my gosh, there goes. Oh my gosh
Okay, by the way, I just added a bunch of shorts on there's a it's a flirty diamond and stuff
It's it gets classic. You have to see it. So what's their show called coffee with Kate Kate and Barry? What's it called?
I can't find it home careless Kate like coffee with Kate and Barry like morning coffee with Kate
It's a coffee with a K or it put a C. Yo Barry or not Barry psych
I'll be honest like when I used to join YouTube
I just joined to get drunk now like I actually wake up at the morning drink a coffee and watch K stream like I'm actually
Into this shit now like it's done. What are you into like retort the time each other?
You would like this hurt to say I'm man on Sunday. That's going too far. I think but
I'll tell you this, I have an alt that I go in under my alt and like just type in like,
hey, if I'm doing people say hi to my alt, and I'm just thinking like, if you only knew
who it was.
Well, it's funny because it's like, Sandman is basically like, you know, Satan.
And then it's like, he's having, and then everyone's like, Oh, Sunday service at Sandman.
Like it's an actual church or something.
I mean, it's like, I have people are interested.
I'll tell you my alt real quick.
It's under 10 people.
How many chat people are in your chat?
Probably nobody hardly, you know, everyone hates me. Have you ever seen a guy like a weird ass guy named Russell Austin?
Like in the chat like that guy's fucking
Yeah, you that you know it's not me. It's a gay guy
Okay, and I rub a pair of scissors through your hair and just like chop it all off and put it in a mailbox and mail the beta
Like hey beta. Here's what you get. I don't want you to mail the beta, then she'll say I'm stalking her and
Yeah, do it. She's like damn it, Joe. You made you it's like he made you send me his hair
Right, I don't want to say like when she tries to clone me and make me a sex slave or something
That'd be terrible. I think you Jesus Christ. I think you both are fucking nuts and you both love each other
You just like oh, she hates me. I hate her like come on. You would be the fucking come on
When it boils down to it, you know, you love me no, I mean it's gotten to this point where it's like I
Don't know if it's gone too far now. It went too far like it's went too far. Well, it's it went too far when she was like
Oh, I care about you more than you know, you know, I, you know, I love you.
Get some rest.
And then like, I was like, next time I was like, oh, hi, Peter.
Thanks for being my chat.
Never contact me again.
I mean, literally that's like the two, like, I mean, it's like so extreme
of like reactions.
But it's like, okay, well, you know, I, I'm flaky and you're low.
I don't mean to talk over you and I apologize, but women sometimes they have
their time with their month and maybe she would just like going through
something every day.
I mean, it's an every day for, for six months.
I mean, it's like, I don't tend to move the month, but it's like, not.
the whole month, or a month.
That is true.
I don't know.
I don't like the whole month.
It's been a little like down time.
Well, maybe it's like,
I get like five minutes of like happiness
and then it's like days and weeks of hell, right?
I mean, it's just kind of like that.
Well, I like you both and maybe as best
if you just both like leave each other alone.
I'm going to.
I'm not gonna bother.
I'm trying not to bother her.
I don't go to her.
No tech, these are no techs.
Stocking.
No tech.
Jenny, Jen, Jen, who even knows what this woman looks like?
I mean, I don't I don't know, but I love talking to anybody.
OK, I found this interview about them cowboys, Jamie.
Have that. So you want to see this interview?
Hold on. Put it up in a second.
No, I'll watch it. I'll be quiet.
Watch it. OK. Watch closely.
It belongs to me like a half an hour.
Like say me in place, I'm not going to be quiet for a half an hour.
Oh, yeah, it's, it's, if I've been at click, please have full silence.
I'm just kidding.
Uh, I need to change streamer over here.
So one second, I'll be right back.
I'll be back momentarily with you, Joseph.
Why didn't you steal blogger's haircut?
The blogger still might hear me. Okay. No, no blogger had his airway before you did. Okay. Watch this. I'm gonna share
Okay, here we go. Oh my gosh, the computer is going so slow. Sorry. Thank you, Jamie
Nanny did oh my god that noise it's like so Jesus it's cat. Is there a smoke alarm going off or what the hell is that?
I don't know my ears are hurting
Yo Psyche, there's a thing in my refrigerator,
like if I leave my refrigerator open an inch,
it makes a noise like,
rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, rah.
It doesn't sound like that.
It's like, beep, beep, beep, beep.
And I'm like, now I know my refrigerator is open,
not go in there and close it.
I think that's like a cool invention that they made.
Like, hey, asshole, you didn't close your freezer retard.
Well, Joe, is your refrigerator ready?
So we made a noise.
Is your refrigerator ready?
Can I ask you a question for you play the clip real quick?
Yes, of course, of course.
Do you ever see those car commercials
where like a lady's driving with her family
and she runs a stop sign and she's like,
thank God for these emergency brakes to stop the car.
And I'm like, if you just want to pay attention,
whore, you wouldn't have killed your kids.
It's like, why don't we need cars to stop each other?
Why are you, you know the way I stop a car,
I hit the brakes.
That's how I stop a car.
I don't need the car to stop it though.
I'm sorry, Suggie.
I think it worked out, man.
Why'd you think about saying that?
What do I think about who I'll be right back
All right, I'll be right back. I'll be right back. You're at going now. I'll be right back back back. I'll be right. See you. See you. See you
All right, it's nice to meet you man. I'm gonna go back to I'm gonna try to go back the same as you might not let me on so
I might be back here in a minute. I don't know. What are you gonna do to psyche?
What are you gonna do cry? You want me to cry right now?
Let's go to say man's a calm guy. Oh
Look at that kiss right there. That's what I'm talking about
Look at that love
You Jamie I thought Jamie let me talk to you real quick about football
I thought the fucking Ravens were gonna go in like a nine game streak
But Lamar still hurt, but we can still win tomorrow
They said I'll be back for the Dolphins game on Thursday, but listen
We still have a shot, Jamie. I don't give up on my team.
That's one thing that you'll never see me do.
Oh, fuck the Ravens. They lose it. Like, I hate them.
No, they ain't like that. I'm a real fan, motherfucker.
I live and die with my team, boys.
What up booby
My tickets were one in five. I really would have fucked with the Ravens no more
You know what faggot when we're being good. No, I'm not talking to you soggy
I'm saying all these faggot Ravens fans when we're good again. Don't you come around? Don't you come around sniffing see it?
You see it Joe
What is it? What are you doing?
Joe.
What? What's up?
Are you there?
I'm here. I'm here.
It just takes up space.
What do you tell me?
I just see like a cartoon or like a boxer back there.
Oh, kind of like.
There'll be some, brother.
There'll be somebody.
Joe.
What?
You are disgusting, Psyche.
You are disgusting.
I hear disgusting, Psyche.
I do, I hear her, I hear her saying you're disgusting.
See, you're putting that shit in my pocket, in our pockets.
Are you kidding me?
I like Kate though, I do like Kate, I like it.
I like all of you guys.
Oh.
It's all you too.
Hello, hello, good morning.
Hi.
It's not really being patriotic, but
Is that Paris Hilton?
Oh, it's like, I'm sorry, I thought it was Paris Hilton for a second.
Hi, how are you?
That wig is doing great.
Thank you.
Yes, it's in great condition still.
Yeah, how are you?
People are saying I'm boring now. Oh my gosh.
I'm going to call that a fake.
It's a...
I know, I know. Hey, but you know what? I don't know, things aren't that uninteresting. Like, you know, I'm just like, you know, Vita and I are donezo.
Yeah.
What happened there?
I didn't like how she was treating you. And I said, you know what?
Because she's Kate, she's Kate and Barry, the BKG stands for Barry.
Can you pause here for one second so I can tell you something?
There we go.
I've been in three months loyal to my little member.
Thank you for that.
I asked nicely if you could pause it.
I asked actually nicely if you could pause it.
Yeah, I probably do need to.
I mean, I like, you know, sometimes I make out with the inner model.
I don't know.
The point I was going to make is, this is like, I mean, I never did a lot of bad people.
How sad, you can't honestly be over that though.
I mean, I'm over it, but then she like, you know, she said terrible things to me.
She like, she's told me like, you know, I express sad thoughts.
It's not like, okay, like, you know, seek some help.
go do it. You are not a bad guy. So you fuck her. You're not a bad guy. You don't need
help. You need mental help. You don't need help. Yeah. Sure. And people are saying, Oh,
well, you're like a stop your stop eater because you like wrote your like rubber text message
Um, and really, like, I didn't, like, knowing, I guess, there are a couple of times.
All right, turns off.
I gotta go, man.
I can't continue.
Being weird in my shadow a little bit and spend seats at the next station. They thought it's not me today. Can you ever contact me again?
You know, yeah, I mean your user all the people around you have fun with it. Oh, look, so that was the
That was the last of that
and then I didn't like closely a little something where I didn't kind of like
It did remember when she said just do it and it was like
She just kept going back and forth to like, oh, I love you to like never contact me again
It's like too too much cognitive dissonance to deal with
But anyway, like she doesn't much people like being like that were once my friends now like they're attacking me saying I'm like all these bad things and
It's like I just say to everyone like, you know
She's good at like turning people against me or whatever. There's two sides to this story
Right. There's two sides to the story. No, watch some of Kate's
Streams, you'll see, you'll see which ones to watch, right?
You know, I've watched some of her old streams.
She, you know, she did some good shows on it and stuff.
About like what's really going on.
And the internet is easy to play,
I can't understand stuff like,
and I was like, I'm not interested in like what,
like, I mean, I'm interested in like, you know,
not trying to do harm to anybody, not trying to like,
you know, I just want to do better.
Okay, she is someone that says that I'll go what do you want, I'll go.
Oh, yeah, I'll go.
I'll go.
This bag of ass nigga talk about he not cool and be there because he cool with you.
Instead of you being a real bitch caught his nigga out because he'd be in a phone.
You can't you know, I was it was like a little bit. No, I really do appreciate you like because I think it was joking
But I was I was joking, but like I did see like, you know
Tricky to really good thing called like the the
Scrap metal army descends on psyche or something like that
And you made some comments in there that were like, you know, not not like just like on that
You know just like on my side or whatever, but it's like they were at least like
neutral in a situation where it's like I did like a lot of like attacks and stuff like that.
And I was like, there's an act that you can, I can't even know you like, you know, I'm like...
Yeah, you've had dogfights a long time. I mean I'm not...
The problem with the you and Bita situation that I always said was it was never just you and Bita.
It was always you and all of Bita's army and they always, they would never let you just talk.
One of them always...
stepped in, whether it was Bronzeberg, or was it Sr. Senior, always someone else,
and you never stopped to speak to her, one on one, just you two, and I always felt like they
ganked up on you, but yeah. And it's like, you know, like, you know,
then it's like, oh, well, you can see, like, I had, like, some princess break up or whatever,
but now people are saying, like, should I say, oh, look, what you did to Lisa, and I didn't do
anything. Like, that says, like, people make you shut up, like, Lisa and then they're right
I haven't talked that much lately, but we never had an issue.
But people were saying, oh, you just lead to a piece.
You're talking Emma and Elisa and all these NVIDA and stuff.
And they're saying, I'm not talking to anybody.
I'm not like, are asking anybody, or telling multiple times,
or anything like that.
And she asked for, she told me it's not a contact rumor,
so I'm not going to.
But at the same time, it's like, and then, but I do feel like,
Alexander was trying to tell me she's like,
she sees how beautiful she's treating me,
she's like there's something not right about it like and other people were telling me there's something
like she's basically bullying you and I kind of like kind of like maybe like like the mean girl
kind of like stuff to this kind of attitude in women sometimes that it's like seems like it's like
there's just there's all it was just like it was just like it was just like constant drain on me and
stuff and um I do thank her for everything she did for me and you know I wish her well I don't want to
But I'm getting a lot of stuff like, I mean, it's like, she still screams about like something
happened six months ago, or it's in her eight year of streaming career, and say, I started
like a year ago, and it's like, and I got thrown onto all this, and, and it's like,
and then she kind of like, it's like, now I'm like, garbage again, right?
It's like, it's like under her shoe, like.
You know, say I have to go kiss her ass to discuss anything with her like, so I was like, you know,
leave it alone, let her live.
Let it go, move on, you're better off without that toxicity.
And there's, and it's weird, and it's weird, and then I was longer and I are like, you know, we're also fine if people say, oh, like, she dumps, like, you know, she doesn't like taking water.
It's not straight, we just need to be taking 30 days just to like, because there's a lot of other things going on, like just separate energies and to like, let everyone have a clear view of the situation.
What's going on? So it's a good thing and like, you know, it's it's still a communicator. There's telepathically and stuff and so
Yeah
Occasionally you get a message here, you know
telepathically
Yeah, she heard my voice they say hey, don't look at this short and she looked at the short and it was
It's not interesting, but yeah, but I just want to say thank you KTK. I like your show a lot
It's like it goes on and up like
really like
Really cool streamers like I mean it's it's I'm thinking like I like you and like that's on a number of your stand
Like you know, I like summer
Like I think that's pretty much
I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them, I love them
Um, you know, and I know there's a girl's club and it's like, but it's like, I don't want to be painted like, oh, I'm like
Abusing women or like, you know, it's talking women and all this kind of stuff. I'm not it's like, I've been abused and it's like
um, I don't know it's like
If you get close enough to her you'll find out for yourself. It's like, you know, I was warned about it and it's like, you know
Everything like a lot of people said was true. It's just like a lot of people tell you a lot of things, you know, it's like and then it's like also
There's a side like I really enjoy it about her and I
I like her in a certain way, but it's just like it's been since probably May her personality change to see the
I don't know if anyone else knows but it's like with this sort of strategy to me
And then she started streaming so much, and it's like, and then the two is just kind of like when I almost like when I started
They go streaming so much and they treat me like way too much and stuff like that
They she kind of like started doing on her own show and I kind of started like just being calm and like like doing like
So I would say I don't know I'm not trying to be constant victim counts kind of bad
Yeah, I do unfortunately see your comments. You know, they were blocked up
almost everything. Yeah, like I got Sweet Pea, I got Countess Bathory. I mean Sweet Pea, she was
warden of membership, I hope it wouldn't be broken, so she's a warden of membership to my set.
But, you know, Countess Bathory and Disco Jennie Jen, like some of these people,
you know, I was friends with Sweet Pea or whatever, but it's like, a lot of these people.
Nothing even happened the relationship. I never did anything to them. We're a friend. Everything was good terms and all of a sudden
They're like on the plane one
So what's going on
Before I joined, I was hearing, oh, sorry, go ahead.
You go ahead, you're gonna start to be shut.
Before I was going, I did was listening
kind of what you were saying,
and it's like you was talking about all these,
no, I guess you'd say a lot of them girls
that you've been close to and kind of what am I trying to say?
I hate to use the word parasocial, but I mean you did get a tattoo of either without, you know, that's pretty about as parasocial.
I would say more parasocial is really not knowing the person, I mean it's like maybe you can make comparisons to that, but it's like I did.
with talking to her personally privately on probably a daily basis at that point and it was like
several months into the relationship. I saw her the first time last year probably in June and then
I just like came on her show on October, November, like right December we were like you know I was
on her show a lot and then in January I started streaming the doing the order I started doing
the uh the streamer you know and having the open panels in January and since then she was like right
for like for six months and we got him on perfectly until like May and then like Arthur came on this
show since I met her uncle or something and then ever since then it's like anything goes wrong
everything always goes back to that like how I didn't like kick him off fast enough or you know
and I'm in a lot of these uh yeah anyway so some of the most we went over the uh messages with the
No, here's the thing, I believe people would say something like that from 100%.
I don't buy the doody doody two shoes.
I've heard her say some of the most disgusting things, long and toxicated.
But I mean, I go low, I'm not innocent of saying nasty things, but you have these girls
like, what's the other one?
Not Electra, she's stuck around, but like Vampira or whatever those are, I don't know.
Yeah, or whenever they say he was talking to them, and he was bugging the fuck out of them.
But no one listened to our Instagram or whatever, and then we'd chat under a few alts and everything,
under a last ditch effort to self-assertion.
Sometimes I'd try, but I'd say, you know, might as well try one more time.
But it wasn't anything where it was harassing or threatening or anything like that.
It was all like, hey, you know, forgive me, or something like that.
It wasn't anything.
Here's the thing I'll say about Fakie.
You can say what you want about him.
and as far as like your cats and your place and all that I'm gonna spare that we're not gonna get
into that right now you're ending soon anyway but as far as love bombing I don't see you love bombing
people because I will say that B does a love bomber I will say Alex definitely love bomb
Yeah
And she's going to dox you and say the most, she's going to call you a pedo drug user.
Just wait for it, because she does it to everybody.
I think that it's like a little bit different because it's like I really am not involved
in those kind of things except as a victim or like me.
It doesn't matter.
She'll she says it about anybody that you could know her for.
I'm prepared for anything, I'm prepared for any person to like say, I'll say she's been very steady with me, she's been very, she kind of like got a little offended when I like was a little bit like, confused about the 30 day thing and then she was thinking honestly and people to attack her and I wasn't, I mean, she is like.
has given me a lot of good advice, has been very supportive.
I know she's been very good to you as well,
and she's good to a lot of people,
and a lot of people throw her away,
or just like, you know, jump ship or whatever.
I'm gonna stay the supporter of hers,
and I like her style, and I think she's like, you know, tough.
Really tough, but I think that she's pretty much very fair.
And, you know, maybe there's some kind of,
I think she has intuition about things that she sees things on everybody's sees and not everyone's willing to accept right now that are happening. Okay.
There's things way on in the metaphysical realm. Okay, spiritual. She's going to psychological or not. She's really into spiritual work.
Well, she's far from like a fucking metaphysical freedom fighter.
You're falling into this crazy shit that she does, and you're being naive, which I don't-
I would expect you to maybe do your homework. At this point, I've said what I can say. I'm not going to be the dead horse, but it's not an issue of when she's going if, she's going to. It's when she loved bombed me when she met me. I lived with her for a little bit and blah, blah, blah. But the main thing is, just recently, she started showing my pictures, trying to love bombed me again.
and blaze me again until she realized,
oh, I'm not gonna follow the company line
and just because she blazes me
doesn't mean I'm gonna forget everything she did.
Doxing the family shit, that frets you out.
Listen to this, she said she's coming to Spokane
to whoop my ass.
She's posting me calling back today.
Listen to this, no, listen, I don't fight women.
Why would I public though? I entertained this a year ago.
Remember a year ago she said she was training MNA and going to come knock on my door and beat my ass.
Well here's the thing. You already flaked on this so now you want to do it again.
I've talked about this. I don't care how she's offered me money to fight her. Literally she's
offered to cash her. I think fighting a girl would be a bad luck.
Um, yeah, but maybe it's like, if you like your arms are tied behind your back and you're like tied to a chair.
Yeah, exactly. Or something like that. Which maybe because she wants to really line my pockets.
I'd sit there in a chair and let her do what she wants from it.
I don't know. I think she has like kind of a Layla Olly a little bit nervous.
You might be able to kick her out, I don't know.
Well, I mean, here's the thing.
I mean, I'm a lot better.
I wouldn't be in the deep air.
I'm a lot better than here.
She's a little black, she's a middle age, not even middle age, but she's going to be an elderly black woman.
She's a couple of years, maybe, she's right around my age.
You're like ten years older than me, so you're like elderly at this point.
That's very, it's a very Zoomer kind of mentality.
Well, she's at anything it is, but it's a sort of-
Do you have the same birthday? I have the same birthday, so of course you're part of it.
That's why the same birthday is Crystal Murray with the month that I made.
Astrologically, it means that you're kind of like a certain kind of star twin or something like that.
Okay.
We're not going to record the star twins and put that right now.
I'm just saying, when this happens to you, psyche, don't say that nobody warned you.
I didn't say anything.
But then again, why am I warning you?
You deserve it.
You absolutely deserve it.
Okay.
I'm gonna laugh, and so is everybody else.
How about that?
How about you listen?
Let me finish.
Maybe you heard how on the last lap.
We were doing great things.
Let me finish real quick.
You're absolutely naive, and you're absolutely not a good person.
in my opinion. So listen now. Yeah, you're neglectful of those cats. We see you're up here behind.
You can't just run over me, psyche.
You want your cat by the neck and push it in front of the camera.
I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not grabbing a cat by the neck, I'm not
It's not changing me. Your background, your green screen, so people can't tear apart what you look, what your shit looks like. That don't work either.
Yeah, it looks like a, you know, like a sloppily bit of green screen, but it's not making it terrible right now.
Well, what's behind the green screen is what I would be for, you know.
Oh, god.
It's fine. Regular walls. But walls are fine. I can show you. Like, I'm like sticking in like...
I mean, we've seen a lot of weird stuff.
My house is pretty clean right now. My house is pretty clean. Relatively.
Well, this is perfect to clean your house.
I don't have that to work with.
Sorry, he does not know how to have a conversation.
Since you cleaned your house, why don't you?
OK.
Oh, ghosty.
Oh my god, I'm hurt
You're 10 minutes back there in 10 minutes
Yeah
coasty
Oh, who's the arbiters fuck arbiters, but it goes back there in 10 minutes
Ten minutes. I don't hear you. Well, I'll be back. Can you hear me?
Well, I have to be back. Can you hear me?
Yeah!
I'm foreign in here.
Wait.
Can you not hear me? I can see my fucking thing living. I know you guys can hear me. What's up, everybody? How's everybody doing?
It's good so we're having fun anybody want to join that'd be lovely
Listen up the panel open dial
Thank you for your time.
Oh, let's go!
Horns alive, lights flicker, chat's in the right, and somewhere goes about to die.
Heroes are loud like thunder on campaign, dropping stacks, cracking jokes, keeping the scene clean, the crowd starts howling.
I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
I think it's too quick to rest out.
Can I have permission to rest out?
You don't mind.
No!
I got a question for you brother. When the fuck did I become Indian? Did you become who?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
It's okay. I like hey, I know I sound like a piece of shit, but it does sound good brother
Well, do I have permission to crash out dumb dumb that's his war cry Dana
We're so beautiful. You imagine if we were like I'm first back
Going after each other like arrows and like swords or shit. I
Said I said dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum. I would just be riding naked on the horse with my wig
Yeah, I
Plagged Speedo
You should both be naked if you're gonna fight is you're gonna be naked, okay?
You fucking god, it's like it's hard to be your friend, dude
Why is your gender teasing me?
You're the gender and that's why fucking asshole you fucking asshole
It's okay
Well, listen, don't make me
Shit like that. I'm sorry. Don't be gaining. I'm sorry. I turn straight
Just for you. Well, the ghost wins again. I just turned this man straight. I guess we always wins
So how straight are you?
Male female threesome with good with ghosts
You know you should be a little bit more respectful for a man that actually defend you
You should be a little bit more respect
But I'm in love with you
That's okay to be in love with someone. I mean you can't help it. You should be a little bit more respectful
I'm trying to fucking I defend you on all these channels
Because I would worship your feet
Listen, I don't want that. I don't why you can love me all you I don't want it, but listen be a little bit more
shoes
Listen if you give me $10, I will give you my shoes, but other than that be a little bit more spectral year
Are the Alexander McQueen shoes?
Do you think they are is that an honest question if they are else I'll pay you $10 for
You have to pay for shipping
You're gonna pay $10 for out of shoes and not mine
No, no Alexander McQueen like the fashion designer there was $600 shoes
Yeah, but I'm ghost. He wants a little bit of for his shoes. How much are you gonna pay?
Okay
three. I mean, I can't afford it. I can't afford it. I can barely afford to fix my I have a chain in my in my e-bikes.
Jamie's Cowboys song. Yes, we're gonna do a new Jamie's Cowboys song. I need to. Pretty sure I paid for that.
But you can even pay for my shoes.
Well, ten dollars. I'm looking for a donation, brother. I can't afford it. I'm sorry.
I will let you run let you run this down. Let me tell you let me you know what you should read
Can I give you a recommendation if you don't mind? Yes
Which I read
Can you take that reading?
And let me be all respectful
You take that I don't give a fuck. I gave you all that money
I don't give a fuck about the reading if you really want to give me one you can hear
Okay, you better make it a Leo reading you are reading or foot massage, which one?
I'm massage. Okay
You better make it a Leo reading sir, okay
Well, I want to leave what isn't up the same thing I want to Leo reading but yeah, I want to get involved if you don't mind
I know I'm sure of this here. I'm so sorry
Four cards, four movie cards, and my cards.
Uh-oh, I'll give you everything.
And my animal cards, and here we go.
How many cards do you want out of the regular deck?
Oh, what's up to you, brother?
I'm just here to have a good time.
I mean, at least one.
I'll put you five cards.
Okay.
Whoa!
Whoa.
Okay, so here we go.
Go see, what do we got for ghosts?
Okay, ooh, okay.
Do you mind if I talk shit while you talk? Yeah, good
So there's the ace of cups and that's like a new
Something that's been given to you that will make you really happy something that will get your blood flowing get your excitement up
Get your emotions kind of charge that comes that's coming out with this
this aid of pentacles
this aid of pentacles is like a collector is like, you know, finding things that you want. In this
case, this guy has these women's heads. It can be their hearts and minds, maybe. I don't know,
but there's some kind of collection going on to do with like something that's making you happy.
You're in the process of collecting something. What else do we got? Oh, we got a tower. There's
Unexpectedly unexpected. I don't think it's gonna be a negative
Shake up necessarily I think I'm getting the feeling this tower is gonna be something that's gonna be
There's gonna be
Oh
And look at near the emperor you got the emperor you're it's gonna bring you to this
Having all the four kings
We all know your passions the charge of your emotions. Um, you know wealthy
and uh
you're able to cut off what doesn't serve you.
And finally, we have, ooh, this King of Swords energy.
Amphis is on the, cutting off what doesn't serve you.
Obviously, I am the King.
I really cut away.
I like to be the King.
I like to be the ghost.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I love to be the ghost.
The emperor is all the kings in the deck
and that King of Swords is the heart.
No, I thought the emperor, I'm the ghost.
Okay, and I have one card for you.
Uh-oh, okay.
I want to get for you. I got you. You got the caribou. Why in?
Caribou says
cycles of life rebirth and abundance. Caribou make long annual
migrations and are associated with the cycle of life.
The herd.
or that something people believe that the
caribou returned to them and
my lights not on. I'm sorry to turn my light on.
Hey Lenar, can you get off my battery for a second?
Sorry.
Come on dude.
Sorry, it says that the Inuit peoples believed that the caribou returned to them each season as the souls returned to earth after death
Taking the form of either beast or human in this painting different animals including a polar bear
a goose and
And others appear with the whole body of a caribou
This composite
And recalls the inuit belief universal soul and so there's actually other animals in there mixed in there, too
Okay, can you pull up the line card and read what that says?
Yeah, sure
Yeah, thank you, brother
I mean I can tell you about lying. I mean you're a Leo. So obviously you're gonna have a connection to the lion
Can you read it to me please? Yeah
Thank you very much. It's very even a lion in here. I'm not sure
Oh, here it is. Okay lion am I being rude by saying that I just
Right if you feel it calls you symbolism courage strength healing protection life
Lion's been a powerful symbol of strength and courage culture on the globe because
Main and light color it has been associated with the sun
with them and the source of life and energy. In Buddhism, the lion symbolizes courage,
nobility, and good luck. In medieval times, the image of a lion was a symbol of healing
as it could cure any disease, as well as protect the traveler from harm.
In this painting, a lion is formed in a circle with four points, which forms a mandala.
You see it's in the circle right there. The mandala is a mystical circular symbol that in Buddhist and Hindu traditions
Points that would be a square
Yeah, but no, but it's four points like it's like a compass like you know north-south either way east-west, right?
And that's kind of like a sideways square
That's not even a square. That's not even a fucking circle. Okay, whatever. It's a mandala. It's a it's a it's a it's a it's
It's four-point a mandala. Okay. Anyway, it says a mystic circular symbol that I'm booze the Hindu myth the traditional uses a to meditation
Psychologist Carl Jung said that the circular mandala and its characteristic war points
circumscribe the holy place. It was a means toward greater self-awareness.
There we go. That's for you too.
The size what do you mean you have to have like four points to have a fucking circle?
Technically you can have one point have a circle if you make you make a cross inside the circle and it makes four points on the side
You're talking about the taro ring. Listen. I am a Leo. I am the man
Okay, you're I am the ghost
You are the ghost. Yeah, sir. I am what do anybody like?
Okay, so I am the man
Me okay, so I'll mention the German. He's getting some Star Wars shirts in the mail. I think
Can I say no my dumb dumb shirt if you don't mind we can actually guys if you want to send him a Lenore hoodie
There's some Lenore hoodies available on a psyche awakens calm and as well actually suck
I think this would be a good cash grab. We can join together. I'll give you the permission to say dumb dumb moment
Dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb. What's a Star Wars shirt? Hey, what's a Star Wars shirt ghost?
Well listen Mason
Because I wouldn't what I have one question for him. What do you think about Jar Jar?
Jar Jar being
I think he's I think he's I think he's a stiff word. That's what I think like him. Oh my god
You're the only one in the world. I love Jar Jar. Obviously. I love him. I think he's a stiff word
Think he's an undercover support. So have you been listening to what people have been saying about me or have you heard me?
Dude, I fucking debate these people all the time. Yeah
Like they talk shit about you. Oh, you're talking boy. I fucking get there and I destroy them by the way
You say tell them you're psyche's
Bro-bro, okay. I don't I tell him I'm taking some dumb. Oh
Like a lollipop. Yeah
I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it
Nick John let's put up a time up here brother. Oh, where is it? Oh, it's for you. Nick Johnson. That's close sober, brother
We're having fun tonight
I always want to crash the fuck out crash out just hold on a second. I don't see the crash out
Downloads. Okay, I'm playing that shit, but we're talking. Okay
You mother fucker you did it anyways. Oh, I I was already had my finger on the trigger though
It means he goes I didn't mean to I'm sorry ghost. I'm sorry
Don't hit me. Don't hit me. I promise. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna hate you
You say you literally did that this strike me didn't know
Yeah
Yeah, you did Frodo bad
Frodo a hagym
Have to go down
We're having a panel dum-dum they stand by I'm just trying to show Nick's I'm there's nobody else here
What do you want you to say hang up on myself Nick Johnson come up on panel you have to see this in life
And Jamie come up. Please somebody come up and just talk I get I swear to God
I won't debate you. I I swear to God
And when I swear to God, I actually mean it. I won't debate you just join
Yes, he won't bite. He was his bark is worse than its bite. Okay. Yeah, I think I think that's correct
I won't try to debate them. I know that's what they're worried about
Just like join we can talk we can have a fun time be knocking out. Oh
My god, I so many of my these things fail. That's crazy. I'm under a lot of credits for this. Okay. Okay, so it's one one
Go so you there
Yeah, okay. You have to hear this Nick Johnson is there. Okay, Nick Johnson ghost is here. Okay, everyone's here
Okay, fuck you make jacobo up. If you don't mind
Okay
Did you didn't I think Johnson on the panel yet? Oh
My gosh, how do I
My gosh, nothing's working right now. I don't understand my computer's going crazy. That's okay. I got you brother
I got you. Hey Nick Johnson, what you're saying about me goes first one
He says he likes you. Oh, who's calling me? Oh
He's my fan
Well, at least I got one fan. All right, that's that's fun. No
That's awesome
So
Oh
Nobody answered me. Okay. Yeah, it's not working brother. We're just gonna have to run this shit ourselves. Let's run one
Well, am I sitting on the mouse or something? Oh?
my gosh, oh
My gosh, it's not stopping. I did I'm gonna fix it. I was on test manager
So this man have my back or not. That's all I want. Of course. I have your back
No, not you the dick's awesome. Yeah, my back where'd he have the other
I was like 20 seconds, I'm not gonna get back here
Nick Johnson dumb dumb
And rolls in like a fever dream
Eric Abadou hat Elvis Glee
Dr. Paporeca prescribes the vibe
Bill Gates wallet, Easter Bunny eyes
Blue boy swagger, Santa laugh, Tire rolling circus on a bubble bath pass. Showed his butt once, world stood still. Chat lost, it's mine, I can read them through
He's the supermod of the psyche version
Of this mad land
Trust him with the chat, no fear, no fuss
When trolls appear, he turns them to dust
Skinny like a wire, strong like myth
Three bills to buy with a cosmic twist
He's my height, man, guardian friend
Promotes the stream from start to end
Through every life, through every curse
Nick Johnson reigns
Supermodel the Psychiver
He's the type of boy who's boss.
What was that?
Stop playing that shit.
Stop playing.
Okay, well, that was over.
But it'd be nice, come on, that's the next song.
Yeah, your song too.
Stop playing it.
No, I don't want to play songs.
It's not playing.
Here she gots your songs.
Open panel.
Open panel, ghost panel.
Pick it up here and talk to us.
You got, you literally got five more days, dude.
What are you gonna do for me in the five days?
We'll have my dumps with you.
Well, you haven't done anything to me yet.
I'd like you to.
I haven't gave you like a worth thousand dollars. Are you just gonna like yeah, I didn't do it. Yeah, I mean do that
Yeah, yeah, right to me not on
Well, you want more money you're begging for more money
I
Want some
For like two weeks here. What goes to go. I literally paid your paycheck
Your number
Thank you. Thank you. I was just kidding. I was just making a dumb sex joke and it didn't work
Like your dumb sex joke, brother
Because the Capricorn and Leo sometimes misunderstand because Leo is such on fire
Capricorns is like on like I'm like I'm like this like you know
Brush that when it connects to fire I just catch on fire too and then I end up falling asleep and
You end up calling me a dumb dumb
This is like a little life. You might be a dumb dumb sir. I don't know who cares
I was a dumb dumb. I'd be watermelon flavor probably
You know, I don't like
You I did taste water bone the gum in those those lipops is like so like
So they think like bad. It's like not really high quality gum. It's like so thin
It's like all it's like already been like chewed it feels like
I don't know I like when it's like all like soft and like you eat the whole well
That's already let me ask you this question. It's already chewed isn't the flavor already gone
Unless you're you're you're significant others chewing it and you get their flavor unless it's a fresh piece
No, you get there's a live one you know you want to get it
You want to eat the gum that's been in their mouth because you would love it has no flavor to it
Can you send me a piece of your gum?
Can you shut the fuck up and be a good boy?
Yes, daddy
Can you fuck off? Can you like fuck off and like?
Be gone. Let me run the piano. Can you are you see yes, do that question like that?
You run the show
Can I run the show?
You asked what to ask questions, man
How did you feel when you stop beating your wife? That's a loaded ass question, dude
Do it again, I'm gonna fuck you up.
I'm dissapointing.
This goes toberg and no one wake the fuck up.
I'm gonna donate more money for you fuckers to wake up. Wake the fuck up.
It's just over here.
they call me psychies boy
They call you psychies boy
Oh, let me run
Oh, finally we got one, let me run
That is wow
Because you know what happened, gay dog?
One time, I gave him money
for an open panel
Yeah
And then, since I gave more money
and then you got an open panel
Yeah, you like stuck in
Then I was like, you know like
that's a no panel and like
Like the dude that is joined maybe I'm like, yeah, maybe not him. They're like, oh, you you paid to kick people and like I can't live it down
It's been it's like a fucking year ago
Bro, they just gonna these haters are just gonna talk shit
They're just gonna run their mouth just to run their mouth even though I don't even make no sense
They're gonna run their mouth even though they're wrong
Here's the thing though like secretly I love it though. I love the debate
I mean, it's fun. Don't get me wrong. I love trolling and I love being trolled and you know, I like you know
I like the banter the back and forth like
Yeah, oh, yeah, running was the best thing ever man, especially if you're getting ran
Especially if you get run ran on like you know
I've had people carry a new one into me and I've torn a couple of new ones into people as well like
yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
what's up?
how the fuck did you
how the fuck you allowed
Let him blood out. Is it
I'm gonna put you on a
I used to have
Modular house after New Year's
Okay
Yeah, you can say gay or you want second one.
Adios, mío, goz, goz.
Adios, mío, I don't give a fuck what you're saying.
Ay, este.
Let's run one.
Now we gotta go.
Let's fucking go.
I've been trained for this shit.
Let's go.
No, dependen.
I live.
By the way, Sike, I live for this shit.
Let's run it.
I live for this shit.
Hey, goz.
What's up, este?
Hey, guess who's your ghost? We just want to run away with you. Guess who's yeah, it goes you should fake out
Talk to me in English. I don't talk to me at all. You're
Straight up
Yeah
I'm not a speaking. Let's shut the fuck up here
Okay, alex come on up here
What are we doing?
What's one month?
Alex, who's fighting Tommy?
Did I miss something?
We found this at the lake.
You can ask questions if you want.
Oh good. I've been making
For the channel. You hear me? Oh, it's under mayors
All it's under mayors gonna fight Tommy James in a boxing match
That's what did you see the picture? Here's the here's the picture. That's gonna. That's my prediction of what's gonna happen
You said that
Not me. That was me
That was me you sound like a bunch of dumb don't you know what the fuck you're talking about. You see
Yeah
Me that bullshit you dumb dumb don't show me that shit
I'm talking to everybody else in the gym Nick Johnson. What do you see in the when the artist rendition?
We got
You see
Don't show me what you're at weed. I'm asking you to look at the artist rendition. I'm showing on the screen and give me your opinion
Jamie, what do you say? Oh, yeah, I saw it
Yes, one permission psyche
What does it what does it crash out me?
Can I go mother fucker? You're my best friend. Can I crash out? I
Don't know what that means
Hey Alex, I changed it. I learned how to do it t-shirt game. Hold on. You guess what? We have everyone's favorite neighborhood police officer
Hello, yep
My show's kind of like mr. Rogers neighborhood. It's like you've all these like weirdos from the neighborhood come by
They're wearing like, you know, basically costumes
Like I don't know if they got them at the party city. I don't know. Mr. McFerrick is stealing his own delivery. Here's ghost
Hello
Ghost are you there?
Go see are you there?
Is this not a ghost program
Here I'm gonna put you in the center. He's sitting next to Jamie and Alex. Yeah, put me in the center. There you go
So Alex was asking if I yeah fuck you fuck her and then fuck Alex. Let's run one
Um come on it goes Jamie was just in the middle of saying
I apologize game you go ahead and talk about all that shit you were talking go ahead. Oh, no, it's okay
I was just telling Alex. Yeah, if you don't let the fuck your father
You never look at me. Oh, it goes. You literally just finished the sentence. I mean, it's like you just interrupt and start yelling at her.
Respectful lady.
Okay, he was just asking if anybody had any Star Wars.
Oh, shit.
So I change I mean, oh shit
I think we need to get Mason some new shirts and maybe a drum set
If worse comes to worse I can go to like, you know the dollar store and like put something together with drum wise
And we can write Star Wars on them, or we can write like cool Psyche Bruceman, maybe I'll try to get a hoodie donated to him too.
Jamie, Barth, any of you, have you ever looked in the mirror and just like said, holy shit, I'm good looking?
I have.
Hey.
Does that happen to you?
Yeah.
It just happens right now.
I mean, it happens all the time, but it does happen.
Nick Nick Nick looks at the mirror and says hey, I'm Malibu's most wanted
Nick and Nick Nick went to a freak off and I didn't I wasn't invited and he was seen naked
But I saw his butt once
Yeah. Yeah. You're on top of
your butt. You stole my butt.
Yeah. Okay. I had in the show.
Ask the fuck. Yeah. Remember,
you're getting a little frisky.
You stole Nick Johnson's ass.
Yeah, it was nice. What? It
looks good. But I had to end
this. Oh yeah, I think we did
Can you bounce a quarter off it? Can you bounce a quarter off it? Oh, yeah, I get a whole like, you know, whole bowl of burgers, a whole bowl of
pizza that one time. I know why are you going out to yummy's house to visit the dumpsters? Oh my gosh, Yumi doesn't live there.
It's a dumpster night, by the way. We're gonna get taken around nice ass dumpsters. That's my dump.
I know we go to fucking the fight together. I'll pick you up in a limo. We'll get front row seats
I'm going to be her her ring um her in person. You're going to be you're going to be in you're going to be the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to be in the water guy. I got you. You're going to
And I sense will be right be held like a dick Jamie girl Jamie girl. Did you see that Jamie girl?
Did you see that Jamie girl
Hey, what's up Tony bologna Tony bologna? I'm sorry. Yeah, how are you doing man?
I didn't even know that's what you wanted an apology for the bomb. Yeah, once you stop
Yeah, what's talking to me, sir?
How you doing?
So, a fast forward.
I do yeah, I'll be in a speedo with the bit up, but I'm gonna I'm the speedo will be under the
We're gonna take your balls to your fucking tight dick last time a bull popped up
When you have the American flag shitty you pull mom yourself remember that you have to end a lot, but one of your balls pop out
It was one of the
Yeah, baby was there for that night man
I was funny
You can't ins out of the great can
He was doing kind of standing so back you know, don't back us on the couch
He was like look at my fucking oh my ass
And then boom a ball popped out
I didn't do that, I wouldn't talk like that
I'm gonna have to give more money
You see a vegan patriot was in her bathing suit and the bottom was soiled
I don't know what's her name by the way. I don't know her name you guys are you gonna have to put your hands on me. Do you know it's just over
She's the way
There's a crisis
Oh, I got permission that you don't the fuck you're talking about it's got a tober
Yeah
I'll say one more word. I'll fucking get you out of here. Go ahead
That's a fuck up. It's got even better. No, no, no, it's
My outside for a gotty dumbass
It's got even better and ghost over. Okay
Yeah. Yeah. No, get him on it.
Thank you, guys. Can I be
Yeah. Thank you. Yeah. Oh my
money. Take him out. I'm going
to say anyone join in. Take a
month. Minus. I'll keep him
up until you tell me. Okay. So
you're kicked off until he
tells me, but he'll have you
right back at that. Okay. He
can't. That's right. There you
go. There you go. Ghost. Okay.
Uh, is he in the port, uh, is he gonna, I'll tell you guys, is he gonna, is he gonna porn bomb us?
No, you won't let him let him break back
Oh my gosh
I know i'm
Alex are you there don't form one man. I don't trust that man
Alex if you want to send me new photos make sure to send
Oh, Alex
Thank you, erie
Yeah
Remember the score 31 to 1 would you like to run another one?
Jamie's gonna be what? Hey, buddy, don't ignore me brother. I'm talking to a big guy
It says burning joy, and I wrote you a whole song and you're the one sending those pizzas to my house. Jamie lie. You're lying with the pizzas
You know
No, two people a couple people have sent me food, okay, and it's like
One of them, but I will say
Alexander some new food before
Don't
Know he was pumping one night. He didn't really like
I
Some oh crab or something
Yes, yes, and then yes, and then um, I remember that I was looking up shit by his neighborhood
Hey, whatever he wants to do
I
Don't fuck
Dum-dum these are haunted rings
Let me get some of my house
Yes
You're having TPP flashbacks, bro
Yeah, yeah, no one doesn't want to be once that pvp dick you're asking for one be one
Well, so I mean I said, yeah, it's like the piano crack
There's no one we want why why would you want to take them off? You want to talk we can talk in front of everybody
Well, if you don't want if you don't want a piece of it, let's be gone
This isn't the one we want this is me on full screen running the kid
Okay, cop
If you are wrong brother, that's fair. Let's run it run it. Let's run it. Oh, you should run not run
All right, let's run it. Let's run like a top like a top and you're gonna see what happened
And and site is not holding Lenore wrong. I mean, that's how you hold catch only you talk to the site like that ma'am at all
Not for nothing, I thought he was talking about people in the beginning.
I know he wasn't, but it just looked weird.
It does look that way.
So Tom James is a dick, because I saw that.
I don't talk to him like, yo, but then he showed.
He showed a little by the arm.
He showed a little by the arm, but he's cuddling the little chain.
But it does look like he's just holding them by the neck like, look at the camera.
Well, I'm trying to get
He was trolling me the dick, but that guy's just a crazy dick.
And they don't want me if he's going to flip one.
So what's like, what is like here?
Go ahead.
I understand there's no flipping on shit.
Nothing.
What is like here?
Dingtoe, it was Dingtoeber which Mary said?
Hey, you ain't going to fucking out today.
He's like, there's nothing wrong.
Don't fuck with me.
Wait, what's going on?
I forgot.
I'm still
I never noticed that. It's on
it gives the illusion that he's like
Oh, no, nobody's gonna talk shit about this.
Yeah, let's go over here.
We gotta get things that isn't it.
Oh my God. Let's talk about it. Let's talk about it.
We're talking to each other. Look at it.
Is it guys?
Shut the fuck up.
Get the shit.
Welcome to Thingtober. Welcome all.
That's a sexy boy. Very special, less than a week left. So, get on board now.
How's everyone? Hello, Sike. Can I join? Can I join?
The party. A nice fresh shirt. Okay.
Yes, you can
Special for the last week only you're lucky
Yeah, get them things go ahead. I got you back. Go ahead. I'll fuck them up. Go ahead get them
Get what?
Would you like me to get him RL?
They don't know the thoughts they're talking about. They're just stupid. They understand what the fuck the hat
They don't know what the fucking conversation is
We don't
Got even for Alex Semper, and then it's gonna be
Johnny Alexander like I'll burn him up. I mean it's fucking return to burn him up
Alexander and Alexandra is neither a month
Alexander's a piece of shit and she shouldn't
I'm gonna say what I have to say you heard you shouldn't even you shouldn't even have a fucking interview with her some dumb
Who
The passion designer or you gamey flirting with goals
What
I don't want you I do not want you do you want me I do not want you
I don't want you either. I don't want I don't want you either. I'm jealous. Oh my god
You're gonna have to fight me
Jamie sober early this year. Hey, Jamie. Once you take this off watch you
Won't you take this business and fucking mind it once you fuck off the mind it yard? Oh
Jamie stand your ground. You're my top now. No, no, no, fuck you Jamie. I'll go and join. Let's run one
Man what I would do to see Jamie with that hat open the hair flowing in the whole
We're done with you guys
That better be you Jamie, not a picture your brother
Only cool people here is me and thing imagine that
What's up? Nick, you're on here.
Don't tell me that's you, Nick.
That's where I'm at. Oh, my god.
You're doing blackface.
Hey, you just said the end word. Stop it, Nick. You should know better. I said, I didn't
No, Nick doesn't say that. Yeah, that is
What
That's a thing
Never know what you're talking about ghost
I don't either
Hold on. Hold on. Why am I in the bottom and Jamie's on top?
Was it six million no sister sister
You want to debate the debate doing the NFC and AFC fantasy league right now?
Shut the fuck why you even talk man?
Wait a minute
Back to the kitchen, I don't know how can I make can I say I'll say it's what I'll say it's not
Black who do you want the whole series anybody?
You want the Jays? Oh, yeah, Toronto
This is good family. Hey guys you get this new logo. What do you think it's logo? They're losing tonight or they lost anyway
There better be a fucking go song
15 something bro
I
Want to go song
Okay
No
Jamie that's right
How about
Your fantasy your picks
There's some
And then fuck everybody off
Yeah, so
Go some go some shut up. So Jamie was telling us about football. Well fucking fuck the girl
Again
Fuckin bitch, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
Fuckin goldstone, get the fuck out of here, I'm not inside of this island.
You know, was that the one where Natalie was?
Was she the one she had?
Dude, she's got a lot of work.
and I think I know I know quite a few people were up there and I see
I don't think I don't think he
could add it. You're sleeping.
Why did I just panel?
Maybe I can keep you up right
now. That's my panel. Don't
you mean it's your panel? It's
over. How can it be your panel
when it's thing tober? Oh,
did you hear that?
Yeah, everybody's celebrating
Replace broke us ghost over something. Yeah
I'm here. I was just thinking since the bills are not doing good Ravens have a chance to
You know, I was just thinking like maybe she's up to fuck up
Why are you so fucking cruel?
Such a bitch
Well, I mean, you're gonna say how much I thought you did the stuff the fuck up don't be cares
dude
Look, I'm big screen. Are you know that means it's
I don't know. Would you like to see me dumb dumb? Would I like to see you?
You've already seen me dumbass. I know that's why I don't want to see you again. I know then shut the fuck up and be a good boy
Be good boy Saturday night thing sober shut the fuck out shut the fuck up
Join us what they told her
Everyone shut the fuck up
Jamie girl look in the chat
Jamie girl. Oh, did I hear fucking?
Yeah, dude, you're never let that fuck you
And you're a doctor a case who happens
I
Know
And you're a doctor
You're a porn bomber and you're a doctor. Let me tell you Alex has a lot
Available
I don't know
People that dox me though your baby you're getting done
Docs me
Family tree, that's how I operate. So when you hear me doxing someone is because that's me
So I'm just giving a back to you
And
What you should have me go over. You should have the story. You should be your honor. The defense
right? All right. Can you please take out the mist trial? Shut up, ghost. I want you to take the
defense. I want you to kick. By the way, you're kicked. Don't fuck. I want him banned.
You want a band? Are you talking with like a blanket or something between you and the mic? It's so muffled ghost
Are you if you're alright? I'll let me see. Let me change my mic. Give me a like dude. I'll let me see my like
Once you shut the fuck up my fucking does it sound better at all?
No, it's really muffled. Okay, okay?
I don't know. Anyways, I don't
know. Jamie, how are you? I'm
okay. I don't get it. What's
wrong with talking about AFC and
NFC? Oh, don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it. Ghost just
wants all the attention. Hey,
they're getting Lamar Jackson
back soon. I mean, that can make
I'm not a football guy, so I'm
Garbage I'm back online. Yeah
Back in the show. I'm in a show. I'm in a
Go there you go Nick. I was in the chat. I was in the chat in the chat now. I'm in the show in the show
No, that's Athens. I haven't stole that
I'm in the chair. I'm in the chair. I'm in the chair. Yeah
We gotta make one for when we get blocked, right? Like I'm blind. I'm banned. I'm banned alive. I
Got banned. I got banned. I got banned. I got banned.
You know what I'm saying? That's the new one.
What is this thing? What is this thing? I like the Iran that is nicknamed Iran and that's cool
Yes, you don't think that was funny yesterday, bro
With white with the blogger
But when you were like, well, if you can avoid talking about me remember I'm like you're gonna do
You're gonna talk about me and you're like well, you don't have to talk about me if you don't want to and good time
I went over to bloggers later after a while like an hour or something later and he was talking about you and me
And he was probably going in his whole stream and I don't know what the hell
What the hell is Nick Johnson doing? I had no idea
He had me falling yesterday, bro
He was alone. He did the whole show. He did the show by himself. Oh
You didn't know he was alone, right? He didn't know something
So so we were up all that together and he didn't know he was on the show and then we all left and then he was like
Oh, I'm in the show
He was funny as fuck though. He's like Tony Braxton. You'll take an architect right now. Like he's trying to figure out something
Yeah, he's a cool dude, man. Harry was really trying to get to him and he just like
I easily was like, nah, man.
You got heavy pissed.
Yeah, good.
You just work out.
Sorry for my wife.
Go ahead.
I know you don't.
So they might be your microphone.
I don't know.
So we got go.
Do you see what you're doing?
Go see Jamie girls here.
It's Mars.
No, Jamie girl.
Salute.
She's going to know me.
Hey.
Hey, oh my god
But this is comedy up here. I see this shit as comedy everyone's
Funny, bro, if you go back and watch these lives, I'm not just on the floor pissing my pants
You know Garrett from Summers? Yeah, he was so funny. Him and I went over to Vita's earlier today.
He's like, yo, yo, me and school hung out. I said, yeah, me and Garrett hung out all night.
We had a fucking blast, man. And I watched the shit.
Garrett, he's in Summers' chat. I see him here too, right, Garrett?
Yeah, he's coming over here lately. Yeah.
He was defending me.
I don't think he was a fan of mine.
He was definitely a fan.
But I know who it is.
He was he had my back against the blogger. It's so funny
He talks to me about like college games and stuff and I'm like, no, I'm NFL, you know, where the real players play
Yeah, well every lineback is looks like a smash
On LSU and the other team today, I'm like, it means nothing to me
should we uh should we ping uh j1 for you jamie he likes talking sports he does but he's been calling
me commanders and and niners and i'm like good he's playing with you he likes you obviously if
he's doing that oh no i still think the eagles are gonna take the division no worry yeah i do too i
He's a good. I mean, he's a good quarterback. That's me fucking hot man
The fourth best quarterback in the league
Seven with me, but what I'm trying to say is I don't have a quarterback. That's mobile
He just stands in the pocket. That's right. I have the best quarterback in the league number one
Little bills a full of bills. What happened to the bills? I feel I still think that's all right
Okay, it's all right. I don't know Josh Allen. You never know now Josh Allen. You always know he's going to win
He MVP by far number one quarterback in the league number two Lamar Jackson. I'd say no more Jackson all the way
He's number two and number three and four
Mahomes and like you said hurts. How many games into the season are they? They're up to week eight
the other countries. Get their own. Was it Mexico City tomorrow? The last week was London.
Was the Jacksonville over there? Because they play in London like every year. They have a
broke up. Yeah. Look at Miami Dolphins jerseys. They like
I love this. Look at the hat to the sideways. We're talking football.
Do we come here, man?
The offense. I think we spent a little room in awesome.
Now you have the bills on that.
That's my that's my sport football.
I mean, I could tell you the frigging right guard, you know, and the.
Thurman month and one of us running backs for the bills, right?
I'm our Munson. No, I mean Thomas. I'm a Munson died in the plane. He was the catcher for the
What about the monsters? I thought it was Thurman monster. Okay, but Eddie monster with that. I'm thinking of any monster
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
I'm not a top-down swinger
You light up the night
Big brother in the chat
With that wild grin
I was here
Every time you roll in
The fun begins
Thank you ghost
I won't forget you
You need me left till my face turns blue
Thank you, ghost, you're one of a kind
With your big heart and mischief and your quick fire mind
You crack the whole panel, you keep it alive
Droppin' jokes in the middle of the late night vibe
You're the spark in the storm, you're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet, you're still so loud
You'd be here every day
Thank you, ghost
I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
You're funny as hell, yeah
It's always a blast
These moments we're making
Are built to last
Thank you, ghost
You're one of a kind
With your big eye
Mr. Fang, your quick-fire mind
Thank you ghost I won't forget you
Oh, I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
We didn't even hear for it, there he is, he shows up right at the end, was that your
intro song?
I'm not leaving, block out, it's still coming out,
that's been a puppy.
He takes no prisoners.
Enjoy the fucking night, eh, so fuck.
Can I have permission to crack down?
You're too much in your little feelings.
Permission to crash out.
Can I crack down?
Yeah!
You have to say it right. Yes. You have to ask for permission to crash out
You're the produce I'll be direct the scene one ghost crash out action
Bunch of fucking retard run here
Good for running back to
Number one number one in the league. Yep number one. I tell you cookie though. Where do you where do you rank cook?
Let him go and now he's
Did you watch
You watch hard
You did
Yeah, you're awesome. How like funny is that that the Giants refused to do hard knocks training camp and they agree to do the executive
Back
They look so except when persons would it ended Dex career when he went to the pack
See how karma comes back
You put me in the back
Yo, do you see what I bought?
But do you know what a football looks like?
It's the round one, right? Oh, yeah, bitch don't ask you don't ask question
Ghosty, you gotta laugh at yourself. That's what I do. I laugh at myself.
Oh, you guys, come on, brother.
When Alex says he's gonna chop off my toe and I can only hang nine, you know, just laugh.
Don't laugh at that question, brother.
You're only gonna hang nine, motherfucker, because that's what I'll do on top of your toe.
Don't laugh at that question.
You wanna run one, sir? I'm down to run one.
Run whatever you want. Whatever you want. I know you're not keeping us question. What do you want to run?
Whatever you want. Let's run one
I'm gonna run my new project
I bought a new project today
Fuck up, ma'am
Why she's up there and shut the fuck up
This is now you think that I'm gonna like defend it, but Jamie's a fucking boss bro. She'll step up
Jamie might even fucking
Boarded new projected today, bro
nice
I found it, like, so what's your argument?
So, Marin, you're seeing it just good luck, bro.
I don't know if it's fun with me.
Go ahead.
I found it. Jamie, I found it.
You're not going to know what
you're talking about. What do
you say? Donuts. Donuts. Oh,
you're always thinking about
donuts. What do you mean? Donut.
What's your favorite donut ghost?
No, we're not going to answer that.
It's uh, I was upset. You didn't know what the mystery flavor was
It's blue go ahead. It's blue. You're not gonna ever talk me. You're won't we're gonna run one
What is your talk? You're not gonna re-talk me
I don't know what re-talk means you're not gonna re-talk me
What is this favorite doughnut? That's a good question Athens. I know
This fat fuck doesn't discriminate against donuts, I'm assuming all of them was his favorite
What are you gonna kick me again dick
Just shut up. Let me handle it. It's okay. Handle what don't a boy. What are you handling? I want to hear
That was more interesting than don't a boy. I
Was actually learning something
Fuck it I'll work it for you sir
Yo, did you see the news about your shit cuz that just came out
Jamie's cowboy, so wait your favorite team is the Dallas Cowboys
And that's famous
It makes your hero so
Anyway, saying
He's got more than anybody
I agree with you though what you just said bro
What about his dad though, do you know Barry sins his dad you know about him?
I think so I forgot about
I would you know Alex, you know what his dad says during the whole of fame speech for his son? Wow
Thumbs up to the mic and he goes now now my son is
Is known as like the greatest running back of all time, but he's not Jim Brown is like that's
It was like real
But if you watch the film
You can compare them and just Barry Sanders was a whole different like league right or special
They were both almost like a Jordan like no one can compare kind of thing
Sanders is a Kobe bro and Brady's a Jordan. It's gotta be bro, right? Brady's the dick, but
I fucking hate him. He's the greatest player of all time. He's Michael Jordan, but I just I hate him
Come on my bills fan, bro. And plus he's such a dick one. I don't jizz out
Because of that because I love Tom Brady. I always have a Tom Brady jersey
And I'm a Yankee fan one day
I woke up like oh fucked up and I took a go move my car in the morning
So I wasn't thinking so I just threw my Brady jersey on and the Yankee hat and I went outside and I almost got killed
People are like, yo, what the fuck?
You can't have a brain, Jersey, only a Yankee head.
I was like, I'm starting a riot.
I was like, they're right.
I was like, they're right, though.
What am I doing?
I went to Philly, bro, to a Pearl Jam concert.
And there was the Yankee game.
It was the World Series Yankee Philly.
And I won my Yankee jersey down South Philly.
So we were fucking fine.
so we can fire crack a rabbit bro a lit motherfucker fire crack let's see that's funny
they're trying to blow you up what go see that's it serious man yeah that's why i watch this uh
thank you for the deed is i don't say fuck that shit all right watch this we're disappearing one
I'm sorry. Well, that's what
Hmm
What
Ghost are you there? Yeah, I'm here. What do you have problems me kicking everybody else?
You not in particular. No, I mean
Whatever if you want to expand on it. I may have a problem with it, but as of right now, I guess I'm okay
Why did you kick everyone?
Everybody's over talking each other. I mean, we let's let them back us like let's send back one
At one like I'll defeat their arguments 1v1, but I can't do like a verse one. Oh, you're gonna do
1v1
You guys really want to run out. I'll do a first one
Well, let's do 1v1
And eight you want to take on eight Barry Sanders and then Lawrence Taylor
That's what my two players
Do do sports are you allergic to sports or something dick?
What do you want to talk about let's run it let's run it
I'm sick of your fat ass. Let's run it. What do you want dick?
Think you throw a couple hundred around you're gonna just ping pong people with your panel. That isn't even your shit head
You should save your money and start your own panel at that in that case, right?
That's what I was thinking. He's a hundred. He's a hundred and you just kick people open and now you're asking thing
That is do you do you like that? Like what is wrong with you dickhead?
You're turning you like you're going down the ladder hole of insanity, bro
Don't let your mental health slip because it is YouTube shit
Jamie still she's gone now
What a power trip dig you're turning worse than Christine
With Jamie girl ghost you put her in the bag. You put it back. Yeah
And the sad thing is you got to give money to do it
Other people can do it without giving money. I don't say drop the whole plan. I'll drop you really in the back
I'll go in the back if she can come up like that's not cool
It's not even ghost or anymore. That's how much of an answer you being that is
Like I said, you can kick me but don't don't keep her in the back. That's not cool
No, I think she dropped on her own. He didn't kick her. Why would he kick her? He kicked her too?
Yeah, he kicked me.
What's her name?
And then he goes, it goes, Alex, it goes, Sting, how are you?
Well, she's not even in the back anymore ghost. You just
You didn't have the attention
He's just going bro. He's just
I don't know he don't hear
You know what I'm saying I will
get ready to get picked against
school because it's coming.
I was really enjoying my conversation.
It's gonna be him and think that is again for two minutes, and then he's gonna be all alone like all right
Let them back up. Thank you. Let them
Money's worth with his stupid under dollars donation. I guess he's trying to get his little money's worth
Look at that kind of buy power
Look at that
Hoverboards
Benefits like he's the one reaping the benefits man of your fucking atrocities
Don't crash man don't crash. Oh, did he bounce or did he get kicked?
You I'll be honest with you
Jamie I sound sexy, but she probably sounds like she can do more than me like she don't point right with no
Yeah, she's good. She's one of those. She knows more than bro. I don't know shit about football
I like the Giants, you know, I don't like follow it like that. Yeah, I do
Football yeah, you know, she's a fucking that who's winning then they'll see like she's into it. That's right, which is hot
Yeah, yeah, he's awesome. He's awesome. It's almost like oh when you get a girl that knows how to drive stick ship
Like that is hot.
Oh, dude, right.
Great fucking come on, girl.
I know girls that don't even know how to fill up their own tire,
bro, girls don't know shit about cars.
Oh, man, it looks like I'm here with two New York City dudes,
man.
I'm from Long Island, bro.
Long Island, Strong Island, New York.
Oh, OK, all right, all right, all right.
But I got the same Brooklyn accent.
I got the same Brooklyn accent, but.
So everything that is, we got caught up.
We got it.
Jamie does it to us, man.
That was the other thing Alex, right thing when I'm over there. He's like this. I know this is fucking Alex
That's who this is actually this is
Yesterday, do you remember things that I don't know why your voice is a little higher pitch than mine
But I guess we saw in the same here and there's a lot of times I heard it and I was like, wow
We like I already I get it what people
I've heard a few people say
Yeah, we are
But people that really know it's like summer like she'll never like she'll know it's different
My shit's more nasally, right like a little high as one nasally like yeah
That's exactly what it is a little more
Well, isn't this something?
And I was just gonna hop down to get a coffee
Ghost you're back
Imagine that everybody's gone besides staying imagine that who made that happen. I
Don't know what's going on. I
Could you think made that happen?
God
Nope. Who do you think made that happen?
Wasn't God?
Nope. Guess again.
Caesar?
That's what, with my powers,
I'll let them all back up here.
Go ahead.
Go ahead because you're gonna need someone to talk to I'm gonna go grab a coffee because I'm okay
Okay, I'm gonna mute up and go get a coffee go
Spunky thank God
Spunky can handle ghosts
Spunky come up here and tame this asshole
Go ahead spunky. I'll fuck you up and I'll fuck out stuff. Let's run one with a little boys. Hi. I'm spunky
We broke up we're back together
By the way funky the spunky nader and that JT dude
Is that his name? Am I getting it wrong? Hmm. Either way, she knows what I'm talking about.
The bold... No, I don't know what I'm talking about. Because everyone's bold a bit and I don't think that is.
Oh, he didn't hear me. He's getting coffee.
So JT, the bold dickhead, they're fucking... What is that? They're swingers.
They're swingers and they want me to fly to whatever dumb state they're in and fuck them both.
And I'm not doing it, spunky. You hear me?
Not doing it. Oh, fuck you.
He can maybe film through a window
That's the deal
And so psycharone is
Snap my fingers push a man snap of my fingers
Spunky come up here and I should flash her tits. I missed it one day. They were flashing tits and I missed it. I
Want to see if she has nipples because someone doesn't have nipples
I've seen summer with like a bro off and I couldn't find the nipples. I think the tattoos hide it
I think the tattoos are hiding some of his nipples. I swear to God. It was like, you know, it's like a puzzle
I'm like where her nipples I couldn't find nipples
Maybe when the tits get too big than nipples. I don't know I
Believe I'm lucky should have nipples. I know page has nipples. You can see him popping out through a stupid tank top
No, well has nipples
Alex hey
You do I need to yeah, you got big ones right they come out like string beans when you get horny do they grow?
Alex, what is wrong with you? Nobody?
I
Want string bean nipples in my mouth, baby, you know exactly what I want you are nuts
Let's walk. Let's walk you to fuck us. Like what do you want you're talking about? Yes, you guys said that once I remember
Fucking with you, but that's not for real. We're just messing with you
You guys want me to come with all my money you're running your mouth about stupid shit. He's a troll. Have you noticed?
Nobody wants to fuck out
Now you're back together either nobody. Yeah, you're back together
We're back together
Don't fucking out because it's gonna happen again. I've I already see the cycle
I've been through your kind of relationship
I'm because he's gonna be a dick again. You know what it is with him. He's jealous
Because this happened when you started your panel check this out
Everything was fine and dandy with them, and then she started going live and like showing her bulls on
Dumber
Being a girl having fun and that little flag got jealous for the show and gave her an automaton
And even broke up with her just out of control literally do this because you know what?
Let me see though you did why no hair that'll do it
Yes, I'm like you know the fuck you're tall. Oh dad, why'd you break up with it?
Honestly, he doesn't want to move in
He doesn't want to move in you guys are like married. What do you mean? He doesn't want to move in
He sleeps every day clean on your couch. You're in the kitchen when you dump dogs and cats and he's behind you like 40
You don't know the fuck you're talking about you know, basically he's scared. He's scared of losing like his
He doesn't want to commit fully I'm building a putty for us and he doesn't want to move in
What
And he won't move in what a loser Jesus. What's he doing just farting on your couch every day like I don't want to
Bro you gotta move in it's family time. Here's what's weird Alex like he wants to have a baby
Yeah, but he doesn't want to move in but he doesn't want to move in
Okay, no, no that means he's fucking insane
So he wants to keep you tied to a wall with a chain and a baby, but he doesn't want to move in
Bro, if you're gonna have a baby with a girl, you better marry her. Don't fuck you talking about I want to move in
Well, here's the worst part Alex. Jesus
Process of like having the baby and it's it's gonna take like you know like six or months to do it
To grow a creature in your stomach. Yeah, baby have a and but it doesn't want to move in correct
No moving in like you what if he lived now what what good life what a little kind like what's he doing alone?
Oh
Does he ever go on the side?
Yeah, think about the shit like why doesn't he want to move in like a son all of a dumb bitch
Is he baking in his own forts right now is he doing a Dutch oven wake as ever
I'm, I'm making my own parts right now.
All right, let me go get them.
Same.
If I had you, baby, oh, baby.
Yeah, look at how pretty I am.
Look at my expression.
Take out the garbage through the snow,
thinner, cotton orgasms, you know.
No, I'm not.
All right, let's see.
Justin, are you free out here?
And you will have to actually get it done in a minute.
You're actually staying out here, you know.
Did you lose weight?
Did you lose weight, Sparky?
Yeah
We went to the airport to watch some planes like
Land and fly off and we saw like a transformer blow off and the blow up the distance
Plane crash what
What the fuck does this have to do with a baby?
He doesn't want to talk about that.
Oh, he wants to talk about transformers.
OK, I want to do that.
I don't want to talk about babies.
You told me me you guys are assholes.
You probably have like five kids together, right?
You just guys are trolls.
You're trolling me.
There's no way.
There's no fucking way.
No, no, this is my life.
This is my fucking life, Alex.
This is why it's so sad.
And that's why you cry and get hurt because you want commitment. You finally want to be together every fucking day not him 40 minutes away
Coming here and they're farting on your couch. Yeah, you want the whole thing
What can you do it though? Why can't he what?
I'll commit fully completely fully your wife. Yes wife. You're gonna have a baby you live together
You're gonna die together end of story. Why can't he commit to that?
I don't know and it's really probably that his mom left him or something. He's
Pull out the board card again
His poor, ugly ass knows how ugly he is and how beautiful you are.
He knows eventually he's just going to get uglier and uglier, and you're
just going to be the same hot, spunky, and you're going to leave him one day.
That's what he thinks and is retarded mind.
So he doesn't want to jump into the shark tank.
Look at that.
Why would you stay with him now?
That's what he's thinking.
Why would this beautiful woman be with me now in 10 years?
She's out. Five years probably. I won't even make it. So he's like, why am I going to move right now?
Just to move back out in five years when she leaves me for a real man and
I just broke the case. Kaboom. I'm here all week. I do bar mitzvahs.
Alex, do you go into every relationship assuming it's going to work forever?
Or do you always think do you always have that doubt that this may not work out?
Alex
Because it's just what you're saying. I just want to understand the way you look at her look at him
It's not gonna get better for him
It's she's always gonna look this way and when a man comes along that wants to commit and it's stuck in her
Dick like let's move in together, baby and gives her everything she acts
She really wants this little bald dick is gonna go fucking crying and that's what he said
Maybe what if that is
There's a man out there that wants to move in with her maybe and what if that is
When there's a problem I just saw his little Lex Luthor as like running the kitchen. Yeah, I just
What is he scared of the camera you Lex Luthor
Little fuck I would be he probably doesn't want his private life being disseminated
Issues look at her. I don't move in. I don't know you're 90. Yeah, so let's lose or you're not
What are you waiting for?
Like I can see this a little high school or something like I want to move in yet. I'm too young
I got all my life. I had to meet your how old is he 50 plus everything 55
45 and 45
Basically 90 and you don't want to move in now
Jesus fuck what's he waiting for 55 to pop like bro. You're lucky if you make it to 55
So your hair is gone. That means genetic is not good. Your heart's gonna pop out of your fucking chest probably soon
Yeah, I would be all over spunky, man. You're terrible
Yeah, a cock from how that shit gets hard every fucking two seconds
And I clean up. I'm a, you know, I'm a man. I can I can change a lightbulb and shit
I'm the kind of guy that if we crash on a plane together on an island
I will build you. I will build you a fucking mole out of a tree. I'm all
Fucking tree
This they can build shit punk. Does he even know what a screwdriver is?
He thinks a screwdriver is a drink, right? It's vodka with the fucking orange juice. That's the only screwdriver
You know, okay
Okay, she had sponkeys here and she hears you saying all these things
And then she's got Jason just coming right now. Why do you think she's like
Like she actually knows what Justin's like for me, it's just worse
Did you forget that this guy had her crying a month ago?
We she was crying. I saw it. We broke up. He left me. We broke up. She was hurt
And now this black fool's the dick is running around hiding in the kitchen
My god, and you're just and you're just saying you deserve better
Step up to the plate or get the fuck out of there and the story you're wasting your life and hers
Honestly now for nothing if she doesn't make you happy go find what makes you happy, bro
I know that's what I've said. I don't get it. The clock is ticking exactly because he's crazy
So you know what? He doesn't know what he wants. He doesn't know what the fuck he wants
He wants you get he doesn't he doesn't know next thing. You know, you're gonna be 60
Waiting for this bald dick by then. He'll be fucking dead in a wheelchair like come on
If spunky leaves Justin, you're you're in there, right? You're you're promising you're gonna be there forever
Alex is married
Yeah, yes
I looked him up here. Oh, really? Yeah
Okay
Yeah, I'm in there man. She's used that asshole. Yeah, you're gonna be there forever, right?
I can see her toes, bro
Did you see pages feet? Oh, that's why I know she's a keeper
Let me see them feet
That's that's the test
All right, well, I guess I shut ghost up I didn't hear him at all I came up here to save you Alex and then you just grilled me
Wow
All right, so you're gonna go get anti-freeze put in his coffee and give me a call
Please if I was gonna do something to be insulin between the toes
She knows how to do things right
antifreeze. Don't find that out right away. Straight to San
Juan. Yeah. It's one naturally person your body. It's really hard to figure out if it was exogenous brought from outside the body or and then you can just cut the feet off and toss them in a river and don't even they'll never figure it out.
How does it that's messy?
Well, what's you know, that's where you're like a little whimsy, huh? Alex, that's where you're for you're there to dispose of the bodies.
When you coming down, well, I'm Colombian. I'll just put them in the acid and flush it on the toilet
That's the best way to do ever glades
No acid you put the body in acid it melts it into liquid and you flush it down the toilet
Have fun with that forensic team
Like where's the body like yeah
I think there's a way if you dump on the gator so they can go in the gator's stomach and find human body parts
Acid is the best way to do it. Think about it. No no bones nothing
It turns it into liquid like water and then you just flush them down the toilet
Bye
No, nothing
Think she don't forensics to you trying to figure that shit out
Like unless you can
Yeah
This is the thoughts his train of thoughts how to dispose of human bodies
Poor J1 he probably has so many questions
No, he probably came on to talk about the Jays the Toronto Blue Jays
Do you want do you have any questions for Alex?
No, I'm gonna say this won't be there. You're pretty smart and you work look good. Oh, they're clean
I just saw her toes again. She waved them to like the left and they just appears you know
I
Don't think it's for peering left and right behind their head. Do it you guys are nuts
Do you take I was just making a little movie of oh my god imagine what kind of what panties she has on right now
Jesus fuck
Oh, Jesus. Yo, where's Lex Luthor, bro? What a dick.
Tell him. Alex, did you ever see him in here? Tell him. He doesn't know what he has.
Exactly.
I know.
Oh, it's your back. How come you keep dropping, man?
Yeah, Gus, what's up? I came on here to, like, mess with you. Are you broken?
Oh, you came here to mess with me. Go ahead.
I just wanted to say hi. How's your life?
What what you meant to say was you came here to say hi you didn't come here to the mess with me
No, I came to mess with you. You know like
No, no, no, I didn't come here like beat you up. I just came here to be like
You really
Ghost you have a woman taking some interest in you. Why are you fighting it?
Him her then you can get like six seven eight nine people
You're never gonna mess me up. You don't understand that right? No, no mess with you not mess you up
There's a difference. I was just saying hi and like shaking your night up a little
It's important about the acid thing is getting that acid because it's not like home people acid. It's a special acid
Yeah
High-grade acid my man just most anything
It actually turns pink, and it's like a bubbly pink.
I was supposed to have bubbles too.
Yeah, it looks like pink.
A lot of gas.
So what a big y'all?
Wash it on a toilet later, but I'll take months to
No, that's it take months, and now we take days like a day or two. What I'm saying
There's no way
Alex said the chemical reactions for the body to break down and the chemical reactions the energy that would be released
No way
I don't know how those acid things are in, like, plastic barrels.
I don't know how it makes sense to me.
How does it not go to plastic?
Special Colombian acids.
Special Colombian acid.
It eats everything.
So, acid only eats, like, the meat and leaves the bones.
This acid eats everything, the bones, everything,
into pure liquid that you can just literally flush it down
the fucking toilet or a fucking sewer.
Don't ask me.
I was watching.
You get turned into liquid.
Buried in the backyard. You ever seen that episode that show? That's the stupidest thing on earth. Why would you do it?
No, no
Someone bought a house and in the porch like underneath the porch they went down there
And there were all these barrels and they opened it up and it was like bodies and asses
Can you fucking imagine
No fucking way dumb dumb we didn't see it dumb dumb in Colombia they do that for breakfast
People disappear with breakfast
You just a dumbass bitch
Look how hot she is. No, she got the black
Ghost is so mean like I don't I came on
And and now you're calling me a dumb dumb
I wouldn't follow you
Fuck I can almost guarantee that I'm more educated than you are
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
I want to ghost is blocking my picture. Can you move him out of the way?
Get that dick out of the way
He's in the middle of the screen. Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Move go side of the fucking way
He's blocking my picture, bro
Alex is gonna make all these little Jeff's thing. How are you doing?
Cool
I want the 1v1. You're not gonna escape that.
I didn't get anything.
A 1v1. He wants a 1v1.
I was tripping. I was tripping. I'm like, wait, I'm in the show.
I'm in the show, but I can't see myself.
And then I figured it out. That ghost is blocking my...
1v1!
That's how fat you are, dick. You just...
When God said, let there be light, he said ghost.
Can you please move out of the way?
When ghost stepped on the fucking scale, it's said to be continued
Listen, he's the ghost with the
1v1 with who I
Wanted with her
You can't psych
give ghost is funky
Oh my god, imagine just rumbling around under the covers with her right now just
I
Can't believe that guy's over there, and he's not banging you from behind
I'll erase those eyebrows and paint them on again
I'll do the old Mr. Potato Head thing.
I'll take her apart and Mr. Potato Head her back.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, brother.
It's a funny way to say sex.
You can rearrange your face like a Mr. Potato Head.
I know.
And she's beautiful.
I went out tonight to her show.
But you know she fucks, because any girl with a nose ring
and she's got a nose ring and a lip ring.
That says, give it to me in every hole I have.
That's right, but stuff
It's uh, oh to those rings and
Any tongue ring is their tongue ring?
There's definitely nipple rings
No more is there a clear ring
There was but no more look at that tongue look at that tongue see my dick just got hard
Fuckin bag it
Do your one-on-one won't be one do it come on do it do it do it do it run it run one run one
What would you like to discuss?
Let's run one. I want more of who wants to run it you you're the one that's
Right now at a commission after that tongue bro running with whoever you want
I need a breather
Go ahead. See some girls are hot and some are cute
And those are the golden ones and she's
That's from the bottom of my heart. I feel that way I always did my life. I'm like some girls are cute, right?
She's so hot but the cute and hot combo
That's my kryptonite
And that's you don't fuck yeah, Alex. Thanks. Can you tell Justin so he can value me more?
Sent you white knight you piece of shit and find them where he is over there
He's farting on the couch
We have fun tonight fuck I don't know what the fuck you guys are throwing out once your white nights fucking make me feel weird
We're gonna have a go stop her
Well, who's is that drunk guy at the end of the bar that just mumbles into his drink, you know
Yeah thing is that fuck retard doesn't know what the fuck he's talking about talking about knocking the fuck out
I'm gonna knock you out
Yeah, we run it come on we're waiting run in let's go
Let's run one you guys from the moment. I'm down to run one
Yeah, I don't think I don't think you guys know what the fuck you're talking about. You're right. So start
Educate us. Thank you guys are degenerate. I think you guys are deplorable. I think you guys are fucking
disgusting save me so I
Think that you guys you think it's okay like for two men to kiss in front of you
Yeah, I wouldn't give a shit ghost. If you have a problem with love, then you have a problem with love, and if you have a problem with love, that's your own sad, sad little man complex.
If you're not mature enough in your sexuality to see two men make out in front of you, then maybe you need to get yourself together.
You know and why are you on here sending all this money to psyche you suck in his dick electronically when you're
A little bitch
Sending all that money
Over and over you might as well suck his dick on camera
And then you gotta come on you're talking about two men together kissing in front of you is uncomfortable
And that bothers you because we're
It sounds like your mother raised you like a fucking degenerate, stupid bitch.
Spunky running one.
God, give me the next one, bitch.
You wear like a peony, obviously we're going to fucking judge you and like we're going
to sexualize you.
You can judge me all you fucking want because all I do is come on here and shit all over
you.
She's right.
which is what it said a little while ago it's a it's it makes perfect sense it's like i'm on your
running gibberish you know like saying your mom's shit i'm telling you real shib buddy
you're sending good hard-earned money to psyche who is a gay man and then you're gonna come on
here and talk shit about gay men you're a fucking retard yeah that's fucking retarded that's absolutely
Don't stand for fucking retardation and then you're gonna come on here and talk to me that I'm stupid
You can suck my dick psyche. I mean
Well
You want to talk loud
No, I want to talk real real. I want to know why you're on here talking shit about
this channel. You're talking about know your place, bitch. Know your fucking place. Like,
get it together. No, you're some other person stick up then and get on their channel.
We don't want your offending psyche for something that he is talking about.
Go ahead, prove your place right now.
So if you're listening school of happens is in the back in the back. Yeah, sorry. You're I
Just
Just talk you didn't proof shit. You don't fuck
You stupid ass bitch
But you know what
It's not Bronzeberg wouldn't do anything, but someone might be faking him
No, it's him. Okay
Come on
Ghost is a dick bro stop fucking throwing money around like an asshole because do it for like if you like out of the bottom of your
heart
Don't do it
For like to try to control shit and talk shit about gay people and kick us when you don't like what we say like that's a
Stupid thing and that's why you look at heart it both you want to donate site give him a million dollars
but you're using it against even him.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's so disrespectful to come on this channel
and talk negatively about gay people.
You're not gonna come on this channel.
When psyche is gay.
I don't know.
You realize that, don't you?
You look like a two-buffing, total dickwock.
You're just gay channel, John Clark.
I don't give a fuck.
That's the stupidest shit I've ever seen in my life.
Everybody here agrees with it.
Do I have permission?
Excuse me. Yo, when this guy wakes up, tell him to move goals. He's blocking my picture.
Do I have permissions? Give me permission, brother.
Permission to work, bro. Keep being an asshole. You're losing yourself goals.
Like you're not the same ghost. You're not your spark is
Sponkeys like the nicest person on the internet
You're talking about psyche, you don't know who psyche is you're talking about like
And I know you're on you're talking bad about gay people and I'm gonna stand up for that because that's fucked up
You don't
Give me a break man. We can't over talk. Do you want to talk we can't over talk each other?
You think your money can buy disrespect because you donate what you donate you you can disrespect
Matter of fact, he's so nice he actually does like let's
Yeah
Yeah, go ahead. I'm a fucking good
Good
You just got roasted by one of the most beautiful cutest little spunk in here. Let me see them talk
Yeah, you're not that they're near shut the fuck up like a good girl. What you should have let me go
You don't know how to talk to a woman goes
Go ahead
I'll give you in the back this fucking stream with you running your mouth
It's just like the purest example of little dick energy. I've ever seen in my life
He doesn't realize cool Athens. I don't know what
By the way, I gave you two times the thought would you like a third time ma'am, I'll give you the third time
What an attention seeking war, right?
This guy asked us to just buy attention, which is sad, because we love you before you had to do it.
Now that you're buying attention, everyone hates you.
Think about that ghost.
You're buying yourself into being the enemy.
That's going to be cool.
Not even the enemy, but also just buying yourself into being a dick.
You're kind of like the big
You just make shit the fuck up
Would you like to go but I want to run your gay guy panel. Oh, it's my panel, but take block. I'm psych block Alex
Fuck that. Let him back up. Let him back up. Like what the fuck power trip?
Retorting shit
Poor thing come back for the man
I'm gonna have a little compassion for ghost man
Cuz I know exactly what it is
I'm not gonna go that far and go into it cuz I really don't give a fuck but I know exactly what it is
Just why I'm enjoying it a lot of money right now. If you saw him come up, you know exactly what it is
And you came up earlier dick when you first came on the panel tonight you came up again, and I saw your fat fucking face
again
Which summer remember that that was so far, bro. I'm ghost knowing you nothing
You fucked up one time on summers and she exposed it
That's why I don't like that bitch cuz she does shit like that and then acts all like I'm a fucking
Oh, I'll read you an angel. Oh, there's evil in those veins, bro
That bitch has gasoline running through his fucking veins
That's crazy my little ghostie camped up on accident on summer's tokyo rich one night and she doxed them
Doxed him for a week a
Week his picture had it up there four different people
our school of Athens
Did he drop?
seem like it
Alex too
Yeah, I knew that reverse psychology was gonna work. All I had to write was let's be on like I was being a little humble there
And I was pretending I was pretending that um, you know, he was intimidated by me, which of course he isn't but if I write it
You know, he'll let me in I've been in the back for like five minutes. Yo, I was writing to you Spongebob and smiling at half
Spongebob and Jamie girl Bond and Brunei like beautiful with a head on their shoulders
I love what you said before too about you know being able like I'm a heterosexual male, right?
But I got no problem going out with somebody
Like in like, you know six of us two guys are gay and me my girlfriend and her friend, you know what I mean?
I got no problem. It's none of your business, and they're not hurting anybody. Why would you be an asshole about that?
And you want to know something this grosses out a lot of people what I'm about to say and a lot of people will make fun of me
But like I understand like me looking at a girl is like psyche looking at someone else
I understand the way is the way he feels
So like the way he feels and what he's presenting is saying it grosses him out, but you know what? I'm grossed out by two
Fat disgusting nasty people making out to you whether they be men or women or women or men or whatever
Make out grosses me out to
Yeah, myself and shit that isn't my business
I get close out when it's these two people kids like yeah, you know same thing
Her eyes are all lit up. You know, she's happy to be here. This is just I love it. I'm so glad I ran into you Spong. Oh
School of Athens. Thanks. I had a really good night. Yeah, I like how you put that before because I was talking
Question
Don't make me put it's just it on you stop
The bait club like that was like his whole thing
What's cool happens part of the bait club is that his whole term?
Ashes can you run one with him?
I
Crash like what do I say? Let's crash bro. Is that what we're doing together?
Let's crash out together brah. I'm with you. I'm with you. You're another one goes to when when like
That's like dumbass motherfucker like I went I went to like to ducking ladies and I'm
You don't know fuck you're talking about certain. We never
Ghosts like me spoke. I need you to translate that. What did he say?
I know he's the ghosty with the mosty, you know, I'm gonna
Spectrum the touch of tiz man bring it
Alex, you like that?
I do.
I love him the best.
I don't know why he loves you.
Look at Jamie.
She's so like,
You know what's funny about Gold?
He doesn't realize how much we love him.
Like he's one of my favorites.
I can't talk about everybody,
but I have that feeling like everybody loves Gold.
He doesn't like it when I'm nice.
Like he's one of my top three favorite people up here.
He doesn't like it when I'm nice to him.
When he has to buy, like attention, it's just weird to us, like what he's doing, that's odd.
Ghosty!
Who's that with the most?
It's a million person that comes along that show might not be here anymore. It's like, you know, and then correct
But don't make you but you're making everybody against you the way you're doing it. Yeah. Yeah, I don't it like I love you
It's like yeah, he's on you, but then you're using it like yo
It's my panel and kicking people like that so you're turning it you're using it like as a power thing
And then everybody's starting to like hate you like this guy's a dick
I got some real good shit for you Alice
So, you know, you and I talk, you know, the road the path to enlightenment and like you try to donate like
Anybody's cash up and don't say anything about it. Don't say anything to the person
I'm just
I'm taking so the wrong way everybody's taking the wrong way streamer. You can ask I don't think
That's why I see that everybody's taking this the wrong way
Everybody's being because part of the donating is so people know he donates. So that's why I say that
I don't think the donations are
opposed to me.
Yeah, I was just posing
Telling ghost and everybody has to do that at all
You know you go on and on about things and it's like really like not anybody's really business about it
Justin Justin hasn't come around once and
Drink nothing
Complete
Are you
Second, yep, yep, that's how one kiss and a half unbelievable psyche
It's so funny how somebody like I'm posing a hypothetical you think I'm like being prejudiced
Imagine the scenario
You're a beautiful blonde girl named Sponky in your vicinity, in your kitchen, you ignore her.
You're believable.
I'm the self-awareness.
I love your self-awareness.
Right now, blueberries, you know, it's brand new.
I want you to be able to check in on my Sponky.
Don't eat as much as money.
This guy is guarding on a couch.
He doesn't give a fuck.
It's just it's just oh my god. Did she put her hair down?
Alex is all bricked up man. That's all
It's just hilarious
Yo, fuck I like that left
She put her hair down, and I see cleavage. It's a wrap. You guys
Have to charge my phone it was on 2%
Where is that parting asshole anyway, you see where is the living room and he's just ignoring me watch what he's doing
It's pissed off. He's like, don't put me on this piece. What's wrong with this man?
I don't know. I don't know.
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on the straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline. Yelling till it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Canada dry got gondol, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marseille flashing
Chaos on the feed
And here comes a porn bomb
Oh Lord, we don't need
He's purring.
Christine's with Fuzzy Bear.
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare.
Truckerado rumbles in.
Sammons chasing views.
DJ Electra's cartoon face is breaking all the rules.
We've gone too far, we've turned the trolls into our own mems
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another in-joke.
We're laughing through-